A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Books and Reports Department, Graphic Design FA970
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Books and Reports Department, Graphic Design
1987-1992
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University Press
Rockefeller University.
FA970
1.38 Cubic Feet 1 document box, 1 oversized flat box.
Scope and Contents
Materials include promotional pamphlets, posters, and advertisements for RU lectures, events, seminars, academic programs, and publications.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
File Plan
Former Classification: I 531-U
Arrangement
As received.
File Plan
Former Classification: I 531-U
- Academic Program: posters, flyers and informational brochures (Box 1)
- Announcement, Launching the Antibiotic Era, Eds. Moberg and Cohn, Informational Brochure and order form (Box 1)
- Holiday Party, President's House, Invitations, 1991 (Box 1)
- Journals, Subscriptions, 1991 (Box 1)
- Journal of Cell Biology - Promotional Pamphlets, 1991 (Box 1)
- Journal of Experimental Medicine - Promotional Pamphlets, 1990-1992 (Box 1)
- Lectures, Memorial Lectures and Special Events - Promotional Flyers, Announcements, Invitations, 1990-1991 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Promotional flyers, posters, invitations, announcements.
- The Rockefeller University Ph.D. program: poster (Box 2)
- Second International Conference on Elastic and Diffractive Scattering, 1987 October 15-18 (Box 2)
- The Rockefeller University Pro Bono Humani Generis (Box 2)
- 32nd Annual Alfred E. Mirsky Christmas Lecture on Science, "Biological Clocks", Lectures by Michael W. Young (Box 2)